Okay, have a good night.
[Anzu gasps]
Anzu, you're done?
Heading home?
Thank you for your hard work.
[playful music]
[groans]
What's with these three?
The charm level is off the charts!
[Junta] I was just out for a run.
[Tsukasa] Work ended early,
so I thought I'd stop by.
Uh. And what's all this, then?
Sir, I was just being polite
greeting Miss Hoshino and her friends.
[Junta] It's nice to see you, Mr. Koganei.
Huh?
[Hijiri] You're Tsukasa Kazuki
from Class 7, are you not?
You two know each other?
Yes, I've seen him around.
Top performers tend to stand out
above the rest of the crowd.
Oh.
STUDENTS NOT WORTH NOTICING
Well.
[gasps]
Hijiri, height does not define a man.
What a thing to say.
-Come, Tsuchiya. Let's go home.
-Yes, Sir.
-He feels bad for being short.
-You think so?
[Tsukasa] I think
she's reading that wrong.
[Anzu] They can pretend
it's just coincidence,
but Kazuki and Junta are such gentlemen,
going out of their way
to walk me home from work.
Summer training starts tomorrow.
No break for me, I guess.
-Same. I work every day.
-[chuckles]
[Anzu] This is starting
to feel pretty normal,
all of us hanging out together.
I just wish I could figure out a way
to stop Riri's constant onslaught
of schemes.
-[Saki] Hey, Anzu!
-[Anzu] Huh?
Here I am.
Saki? You okay?
Uh, oh no. Did you not get my messages?
Uh, hold on.
Why are you all together this late?
[Anzu] Uh…
[theme music]
#10 OTHER WAY AROUND, DUMMY
[Anzu] And that's why the three of us
have been living together.
Now you know the whole story.
That makes a lot of sense. Sorry.
I shouldn't have just shown up.
[Anzu] No, it's totally fine.
Trust me, I've been meaning
to tell you anyway.
[Saki] You mean it? That's a relief.
Hope you don't mind me asking,
what brings you by so late?
Um… Well, you see…
I live with my dad and my brother,
and dad got put on the graveyard shift.
[Saki] So then…
Back by dawn.
Night, Daddy.
-[chuckles mischievously]
-Huh?
[soft music]
-Uh?
-Hey!
Get out of here, squirt.
Go spend the night at your friend's.
-Dude, your sister's hot!
-Stop it. Quit being such a jerk.
Sorry about them.
And, just like that,
my brother kicked me out.
[Anzu] Scum!
What's his number? I'm gonna give them
a piece of my mind.
It's already been taken care of.
[indistinct chatter]
[chattering continues]
Enjoy this little party.
By tomorrow,
you'll all be crossing the Sanzu River.
-[man] Huh?
-[woman] Uh…
The hell?
[phone rings, vibrates]
[Saki] I told my dad what happened,
so my brother is dead meat for sure.
[Saki's dad grunts]
You're actually a little scary, you know?
No kidding. Don't let her
girl-next-door appearance fool you.
Saki's not someone you mess with.
Oh, you're just exaggerating.
[Anzu] No, I'm not.
Remember that time in junior high?
You were such a badass!
[Honda] Hey, Saki!
-Huh?
-Hmm?
-Tell me, how big are your boobs?
-[boys laughing]
[bully] Dude, I can't believe
he really asked her!
Hey, how long would you say your penis is?
-[boys gasp]
-What?
-[chuckle mischievously]
-[laughing]
[muffled laughter]
They had no comeback.
They just stood there stunned.
They're so upset.
But come on, it was no more personal
than what they asked me.
-[coughs]
-Yeah, I wouldn't wanna mess with you.
[Saki] I love a sleepover.
-Oh, what a cute cat figurine.
-[toy squeaks]
[Anzu] That's Cat Ranger.
He's from a video game.
Right, I remember that game.
We should play.
I bet it would be a lot of fun.
-Do you still have it?
-I lost it.
[Anzu] Along with every other game
and system I owned.
-That sucks.
-[Anzu] Wait.
Why didn't I think of this before?
Saki's the one person who'd believe me
if I told her about the wizard,
stuffing all the crazy things
that have been happening!
-Uh?
-Saki, I, I need--
-[lightning crackles]
-[yelps]
[Anzu groaning]
Are you okay?
[Anzu groans]
It hurts! I gotta go.
Oh?
-[groans, yelps]
-[stomach growling]
[Anzu] Kazuki, hurry! Move it, go, go, go!
[groans in pain]
Huh?
-What the heck?
-[door opens]
-[Tsukasa] Oh.
-Uh…
[Tsukasa] Good night.
Good night.
You know,
it kinda caught me off guard, at first,
when I found out that the three of you
were really living here together.
But I get it. Junta's such a good guy.
[chuckles]
And I think you and me
have a lot in common.
How so?
Well, not our personalities, but,
I get the feeling we both deal
with the same daily nuisances.
Hmm.
Oh, but you don't have to worry.
Anzu always takes care of her friends.
Huh?
Good night.
[Tsukasa] Good night.
Huh.
Did I eat something rotten?
[evil laugh]
Do you know it's forbidden
to discuss the details of our arrangement?
Riri! Why didn't you tell me that?
[Riri] It was all spelled out
right there in the fine print.
[Anzu] I was supposed to read that?
As stated
in the aforementioned fine print,
telling anyone about our deal
will result in stomach distress.
-[chuckles]
-What is your problem?
-[grunts]
-That's it! Get out of my house!
[Riri] Again with the window?
[groans]
Does your stomach still hurt?
[weakly]
Yeah, but I'll be fine.
Glad to hear that.
[yawns]
I can't believe it's summer break.
Anzu, we need to hang out
all the time, okay?
[yawns]
That sounds good to me.
What do you wanna do?
Hmm, it was pretty fun just hanging out
around the house with everyone tonight.
But still, we have to go
to the summer festival.
-[Anzu snores]
-Huh?
Mm?
[giggles]
[Saki] Anzu takes care of her friends.
I learned that about her early on.
[boy 1] Saki Takamine is so hot.
She's like, hands down,
the hottest girl in our school.
-[boy 2] She's a total babe.
-[boy 3] Yeah, check out her rack.
[Saki] I've been aware of it
from a young age.
Everywhere I went,
people seem to take an interest in me.
Saki, did you really turn down Ogawa?
He's so cute.
The soccer player? But he's so popular.
Sure, but we've never even talked
before now.
I'm so jealous of you, Saki.
Your hair's always perfect
and your skin is flawless.
I wish I had been born beautiful.
[Saki] I wish I had been born average,
but I can never say that,
they'll just tell me I should be grateful.
-[slams]
-[Saki gasps]
-[objects clatter]
-Watch it.
[girl 1] What's her problem?
[girl 2] That's the soccer team manager.
I bet she's jealous that Ogawa
asked you out and not her.
[girl 1] She's scary.
[Anzu sighs]
You need to apologize to her.
Hey, we all saw you
knocked into her on purpose.
[gasps]
[girl manager]
What are you even talking about?
Don't play dumb.
I saw you veering right towards her.
Or are you training for a career
in accident faking?
Ow, my arm! I think it's broken!
What? Are you nuts or something?
-She knocked into her on purpose?
-Uh…
She's probably just jealous
of Saki's beauty.
Get out of my way.
You couldn't be more wrong.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Forget her. She's just an idiot.
[gasps, chuckles]
[Saki] From that day on,
Anzu and I were best friends.
[birds chirping]
TAKAMINE
I can always feel guys
staring at me during PE.
Oh! What you need is a bra
that'll make your boobs smaller.
[Saki] Anzu never shrugged off
my feelings.
She never said I should be more grateful.
It might get kinda hot during the summer.
[Saki] She'd always help me come up
with solutions to any problems.
Then, one day…
Look, Saki, I know you've never thought
of me as the dating type.
But, how about you give me a chance?
[Saki] Mori was a year ahead of me,
but we're in the same school committees.
He was always really nice to me
despite the age difference.
I promise I won't even hold your hand
unless you want me to.
Uh…
[light music]
[Saki] After that day,
he kept asking me out over and over again.
I feel kinda bad for turning him down
when he's being so sweet.
Don't feel bad. You shouldn't go out
with him just 'cause you feel guilty.
Seriously, whatever you wanna do,
I'm here for you.
[soft chuckle]
[light music]
I can't promise I'll have feelings for you
or anything, but I guess we can go out.
Ah. That's great.
[Saki] From then on, we would walk to
and from school together.
We even went on a few dates.
He kept his promise.
He was the perfect gentleman.
He's such a great guy, but,
I don't think I like him
the way he likes me.
[Saki] Huh? You want us to study
for the exams at your place?
Yeah. I'll help with the stuff
you don't know.
You have entrance exams to study for.
Helping me would be a distraction.
[chuckles]
I can do both.
I am a capable guy, you know?
[Saki] Maybe it wouldn't be
such a bad idea
to take him up on the offer.
I could really use a tutor.
[Mori] Here we are.
Uh…
[pants]
Come on in.
Oh…
[Saki] He's been so great
and done so much for me.
I need to be honest about my feelings.
Huh?
[Saki whimpers]
Mori, stop.
[Saki] What are you doing? Get off!
[Saki gasps]
[Mori] Why would I do that?
Oh, come on now, Saki,
don't be such a baby.
You agreed to come over to my place.
You knew exactly what you were doing.
[whimpering]
No, I…
[suspenseful music]
[Saki] I don't want to…
-I just came here to study!
-[Mori grunts]
[Saki] I don't like you like that!
This is over!
[breathing heavily]
[Saki] He was not at all what he appeared
to be. He was twisted and gross.
I felt dirty just thinking about it.
[Saki] I need a shower.
[Saki sobs]
-[student] Good morning.
-[indistinct chatter]
[Anzu] Morning, Saki.
[gasps]
Hey, morning, Anzu.
You won't believe my morning.
[Saki] Oh, I will wait till we're alone,
then I can tell her
about what happened yesterday.
Saki, is it true? Did you punch Mori?
I…
[gasps]
'Cause he broke up with you,
he said you have other boys on the side.
And that you followed him
all the way home,
and kept begging him to take you back!
And when he refused to let you
in the house, you punched him!
[Saki] What?
-[sobs]
-[students murmuring]
[Saki] Was this my fault?
Did I lead him on?
I should have been more upfront
about my feelings.
But they don't even know me.
They don't know anything about me.
All they see when they look at me
is my face, my body.
They weren't there.
They don't know what happened.
And now they all think I'm…
It's obviously a lie.
[gasps]
Saki'd never do something like that.
You don't know her at all,
so stop spreading rumors.
[murmuring]
That goes for all of you.
Knock off the gossip!
Hey, Mori.
Huh?
You need to cut it out.
Spreading rumors about Saki's not cool.
She dumped you. Get over it.
But, she's the one that punched me.
Save it. You're not the victim here
and we both know it.
You're the one
who ignored her when she said no
and tried to force yourself on her anyway.
-[sobbing]
-[Anzu] Did you think she wouldn't tell?
Never underestimate her.
Uh… uh…
-[school bell dings]
-[sobs]
Sounds like class is starting.
[Anzu] Oh well.
[Saki] It had been a long time
since I cried
in front of anyone like that.
But those tears…
[Saki] Anzu.
Thanks so much.
[Saki] They weren't sad tears.
They were tears of pure joy.
-I had a friend who could see me.
-[chuckles]
We're gonna be together forever, Anzu.
Yeah, we are.
[sentimental music]
[snoring]
Hey Anzu, you're the best.
[Riri] Hey, gang!
How's your break?
Are you enjoying your summer?
[slurping]
And since we're talking about summer…
-Yep! It's that time!
-[drumroll]
Summer festival season is back!
So what are you saying?
Do you three want to go?
I'm gonna pass.
I can't eat any of the snacks.
Too many people there.
You were a little too quick
to reject the idea.
Sounds like fun to me.
Yes!
You both really don't wanna go?
-Oh yeah!
-[Anzu and Tsukasa] Uh…
[Anzu] He probably just wants
to take his mind off
his team losing the big game.
Know what? Let's go.
You two go without me.
-Huh?
[Anzu] We can't go alone! What if he tries
to confess his love for me?
No! Kazuki, you have to come!
The more the merrier, I mean it!
Yeah, you know she's right.
Plus, you deserve a night off
after working all summer.
[Junta] I won't be able to keep
my feelings secret if I'm alone with her.
Fine, then I'll go.
-Ah!
-Yay!
[Anzu] And I'll invite Saki too.
[Junta] Great.
And we should all wear yukatas.
It's tradition and adds to the fun!
I don't know how to wear those.
Can't we just dress normal?
Oh?
Yukata? I want to wear one.
Really?
I got this. Leave everything to me.
[Riri] I promise it was worth the wait!
These are so perfect, Riri! Thank you!
-Yay!
-You're coming with us?
Mm-hm!
You three look wonderful.
[Junta] How is it
Anzu looks even cuter like this?
[Anzu] Hmm,
this really accentuates their hotness.
WATER BALLOONS
Wow, there are so many people here.
-Hang on, do you know where Junta went?
-[Anzu and Saki] Huh?
[Anzu] What?
Uh. Oh, excuse me. My fault. Pardon me.
He'll never get through
being that polite.
[Tsukasa sighs]
-[Anzu] Junta!
-Oh, Anzu.
Uh, come on.
What are you doing all the way back here?
[gasps]
-[gasps]
-[Anzu] Oh no.
[in deep voice]
Don't get the wrong idea here, buddy.
-[Anzu in normal voice] Ryuya.
-[gasps]
Are you two on a date?
It's gotta be a date.
You're holding hands.
-Mm.
-Uh…
No! I was just trying to keep Junta
from getting lost in the crowd.
That's all.
-Hey Anzu, these guys your friends?
-Uh…
Oh.
I know you. You were in our junior high.
Whoa, it's Takamine.
With a good-looking guy.
[Anzu] See? Not a date.
We're all here together.
-[Ryuya] Tonta.
-Huh?
-Come with me.
-[Junta] Okay.
-[Ryuya] Who's that guy?
Uh, who? Kazuki?
He's just a friend from school,
that's all.
You can't be that dense!
What do you mean?
I know I said I wouldn't give up,
but low-key I'm kinda rooting
for you and her.
So step up
and quit letting this pretty boy beat you!
[Junta] Yeah, well, Kazuki's not really
looking for a girlfriend right now.
[Ryuya] Or so he says.
All is fair in love and war.
Besides, when are you gonna tell her
how you feel, anyway?
What? Uh…
Look, I spent three years
without seeing Anzu.
As long as I get to hang out with her,
I'm happy.
You know, in all those girly comics,
the unrequited love
of a childhood friend never goes anywhere.
[gasps]
-Hey, what are you two talking about?
-Mm…
The line for the shooting game is gone.
We should get going.
Yeah, okay.
Bye! Let's hang again soon!
Sorry, my dude,
but you don't stand a chance.
Huh? Looks aren't everything.
She's not that shallow.
[Sota] Yeah, I'm not sure
he's basing it on your looks.
[Ryuya groans]
Who knew it was so easy
to run into people at a festival.
I wonder if any of the kids that you went
to junior high with are here.
Doubt it. It's pretty far.
[Anzu] That's true. They probably
wouldn't come all this way for a festival.
-[girls giggling]
-[Tsukasa gasps]
[heart thumping]
[Tsukasa] I know
I should have brought my hat.
No, I can't keep hiding behind it.
I can do this.
[breathes deeply]
Are you getting hungry yet?
I am! Why don't we get some dinner?
[Junta] I can go for takoyaki.
[Saki] I want a loaded potato.
[Anzu] Cotton candy and a candied apple!
[Riri] I want a lollipop!
[Tsukasa] That's not dinner.
[Anzu] Whatever. Let's split up
and all get our own food.
We'll meet back up for the fireworks.
[Saki] Works for me!
-Huh?
-Uh?
Aren't you Kazuki's friend?
I know, it's Makoto, isn't it?
Yep. And you're Saki.
Is Hosshi here with you?
Mm. We came in a group
with Kazuki and Junta.
Really? You're here with Hayami? So cool!
He's even wearing a yukata.
[Makoto] And I bet he looks great in it.
[Saki] Are you here with anyone?
[Makoto] Not really.
I'm my sister's gofer for the night.
I'd come hang with you guys
but it would just piss her off.
So, tell everyone "hi" for me.
Mm-hm, of course.
[Mori] Ah, there you are.
I thought you were in the other line.
[nervous gasp]
Oh. Hey, Saki.
[gasps]
Why are you here?
You know this chick? She's pretty cute.
Yeah, she's my ex.
-Not bad.
-Dude, I'm jealous.
[guy] So, this guy here
your new boyfriend?
No, he's a friend.
Oh? So you're single?
Don't bother. She's a real ice princess.
[guy] Ooh.
[whimpers]
[Saki] Anzu, save me.
Uh…
Did you hear?
The big potato stand
has five new toppings this year.
What?
-[Makoto] Hey Saki, let's go check it out!
-[Saki gasps]
[somber music]
Huh?
[Makoto] I got the feeling
you needed a way out back there,
sorry if I overstepped.
Mm-mm.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry too.
You lost your place in line for me.
[Makoto] Yeah, it's no biggie.
I can always get back in line.
Huh?
Look! They really do have
new toppings this year.
Wanna grab some food?
Yeah.
[Anzu] Hey!
-You find anything good?
-Yeah.
I guess everyone else is still in line.
Huh?
-[Tsukasa] You wore it.
-Huh?
Oh, good catch!
It's the one you bought for me.
Hmm.
[fireworks blasting]
[crowd gasping in awe]
Hey, it's starting.
[fireworks crackling]
[exclaims]
[sighs]
[phone clicks]
We look so cute. I'm gonna post it now.
Shouldn't you blur
the people in the background?
You can't make anyone out. I'm sending.
I know, let's take a picture together
and send it to Arisa.
Uh, I don't want to be in it.
I bet she will get a kick
out of you in a yukata!
-[camera clicks]
-[Anzu] Huh…
Sorry, that took forever.
You all made it back.
Wait, when'd you get here?
Serendipitous.
You're slumming in here with us commoners?
[huffs]
Actually, the first firework shows
were enjoyed by nobility.
Okay…
-Let me get a picture. Smile.
-[camera clicks]
[tranquil music]
[fireworks crackling]
[Riri] Here we go.
[chuckles]
-[gasps]
-[Junta and Tsukasa] Whoa.
-That was close.
-Uh…
Are you okay?
I, uh, thanks, I'm fine.
Wait…
[Anzu screams angrily]
-You did that on purpose!
-I know you loved it!
-[Anzu] That cotton candy wasn't cheap!
-[Riri] I'll buy you another one!
[Anzu] How dare you make me drop it!
You owe me another one!
-Huh?
-I bought this for you.
What? For me?
Thank you for always taking care
of me, Tsuchiya.
-[fireworks crackling]
-Uh…
Stunning.
Y-- Yes.
[Anzu] It might have been Riri's
annoying scheme that brought us together,
but I really hope we all can come back
and do this again next year.
[keyboard clacking]
[rattling]
[mouse clicks]
[Yukana] I found you.
Tsukasa, my love.
A fanfare, please!
And a big congratulations!
Did you fall for my little trick?
I bet now you don't feel like
skipping the ending, right?
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪
In today's world, you can watch
whatever you want at your own convenience.
But don't you think in that process
we've also lost something?
[sighs]
Don't just let things be! Come on!
Let's go on a super-duper happy adventure!
So I can make sure I get paid.
[closing theme music]
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Lo-love! ♪
♪ Here we go! ♪